

# PIYUSH KUMAR

E-mail: uic,19bca1059@gmail.com Website: www.piyush.gq

## FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

## **PROFILE**

Hello, I am Piyush Kumar. A Front End Web Developer based on Bihar, India. I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for the transport and logistics industry. I am currently in my second year of studying BCA at Chandigarh University. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a part-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEBSITE DESIGNER**

#### Endic Crew(September 2017 - September 2018)

- Company makes personalized online robots for the server owners on different platform.
- Developed real-time dashboard providing analytics collected from all the IoT devices for the Sensors product
- Developed Apps for some companies regarding online working system.system

### JUNIOR DEVELOPER

#### Clash Stats(December 2018 - December 2019)

- Developed API for the bot owners for game stats connectivity.
- Designed and implemented of full high server website.
- Created Bots helping people to inhance game performance.

# SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS 3
- Node.js, Express.js
- MySQL, MangoDB, PostGreSQL
- PHP,Python and many more

# **EDUCATION**

SCIENCE STUDENT

Harikrishna singh ucch vidyalaya Hasanpur (2016 - 2018)

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

**Chandigarh University (2019 - Present)**